Ordinarily, this crystal should
change to a silver color.
Huh? But doesn't that mean...
Guess this thing's toast.
Shouldn't we inform Alion of this?
RUINS OF DISPOSAL
- Well, we can slap the usual
"nothing amiss" in today's report.
Well, we can slap the usual
Nothing's out of place here either way.
You don't think someone actually
made it out of these ruins alive, do you?
That's not happening.
After all, the Ruins of Disposal
have a survival rate of zero.
Oh, you like the Lord of the Flies one?
Lord of the Flies?
He once turned an island
of monsters into his fortress
and fended off all kinds of invasions,
making himself master of the demons
ostracized by the source of evil itself.
The Lord of the Flies' army
was ultimately wiped out,
but since the way they went down
was just so cool,
they're still popular to this day.
Sir Tooka...
Adding excess worries would
only interfere with his journey.
So at least for a while...
I should focus on being his sword.
I'm not exactly a good hero right now.
A devil feels much more appropriate.
Goddess Vicius...
You'll find yourself crushed
underfoot one day.
I'm going to be the one
to put you in your place.
Don't underestimate the dedication
of a man who's sold his soul.
MAGNAR, WHITE CITADEL OF PROTECTION
- I can't believe the Five Dragoons
have been wiped out.
I can't believe the Five Dragoons
INSIDE, WOLVES' RENDEZVOUS
- And you're certain it's true?
GANOZEA SIGMUS, MAGNAR'S WHITE WOLF KING
- I still find it hard to swallow that
Humanity's Strongest is no more.
I still find it hard to swallow that
JIN ROWAN, ULZA'S MONSTER SLAYER KING
- I identified the corpses
of the Five Dragoons personally.
We are looking into the matter.
Right. Any pertinent information from Alion?
YUSEF WOLLETTA, ALION'S STEADFAST KING
- Goddess?
GODDESS VICIUS, ALION KINGDOM
- Apparently the Black Dragon Knights
were pursuing Seras Ashrain.
Apparently the Black Dragon Knights
ALMA SENTNOKIA
YONATO'S QUEEN, KEEPER OF THE SACRED EYES
- Neah's former knight captain?
Do we have any clue where
she went afterward?
At the scene, we found what we believe to be
the bloody, torn remnants of her clothes.
Judging by the amount of blood,
we believe she was grievously wounded.
You're suggesting there's a chance they
killed each other and she's already dead.
Anyway, speaking of Neah,
I heard Holy Emperor Ortola
passed away last night.
I also heard he lost his mind
just before his death.
I couldn't care less about the coward who
sold out his own country without a fight.
Either way,
the Black Dragon Knights were our best
hope against the Great Demon Empire.
Losing them is a major
blow to our Holy Alliance.
It so follows
that the heroes from another world
will play an even more important role now.
FALKENDOTZINE MIRADIASORDZIT
MIRA'S BEAUTIFUL MAD EMPEROR
- When great evil comes, Alion flourishes.
Oh my. I do believe it sounds
like you're implying something.
Whenever the source of evil itself appears,
all nations are forced to rely upon Alion.
There's nothing we can do about that.
Every living soul in this world is hampered
by the demon king essence, leaving them
unable to harness their full power.
What about the legend of the God Slayer?
Pardon, but what could possibly lead
you to bring up such a story now?
Are you well?
Sorry for interrupting the conversation.
Do continue.
I'd like to ask you all once more.
Do you believe the demise of the Five
Dragoons was the work of Seras Ashrain?
Excuse me.
Apparently someone in Ulza
is claiming they were responsible
for eliminating the Black Dragon Knights.
They call themselves
the cursed magic users of Ashint.
MONROY'S BLOODSPORT CHAMPION
- The Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters
lies further north from here.
The Land of Golden-Eyed Monsters
No signs of pursuers, huh?
I expect this city will be our
best option to make preparations.
What's that?
The bloodsport colosseum.
Bloodsport colosseum?
Yes.
It's an arena where slaves
and mercenaries kill each other.
The fighters are called bloodsport warriors,
and they can earn rewards by winning matches.
So like the gladiators of ancient Rome.
The duke and the mercenary's
guild run the place.
It's now a prime source
of entertainment for the masses,
but it started as a place for the
mercenary's guild to assess fighters.
This looks like a good inn.
So as not to waste travel funds,
I feel we should get but one room...
unless you're against it, my liege.
You know I'm a man, right?
That's not a problem.
Then I'll guess we'll go with one room.
O-Okay.
As expected of the capital,
this place is pretty packed.
Hey, did you hear about
the Black Dragon Knights?
- Hey, did you hear about
- From here, I can...
Got any new info on that?
You know how they say Seras Ashrain
killed the Five Dragoons?
Well, apparently she's dead!
Did they take each other out?
- Are you alright?
- Nah, she just lost and fell in battle.
Nah, she just lost and fell in battle.
- Thank you.
- Then who killed them?
They're saying Ashint got the Five Dragoons.
Ashint?
Oh, the cursed magic users everyone's
been talking about lately?
Word is they're going around claiming they
killed the Dragoons with their curses.
- Word is they're going around claiming they
- What do you think?
I've heard rumors about them as of late.
Apparently they worship the god of curses.
We are the guardians of Ashint!
ASHINT SOLDIERS
- The soldiers who protect Sir Muaji,
progeny of the curse god!
The soldiers who protect Sir Muaji,
We are his Curse Soldiers.
Now, clear a seat for us.
Hurry up and bring us some booze!
We are the saviors of Ulza!
They hardly seem like a threat.
But I guess it works out for me if
they're taking responsibility
for offing the Black Dragon Knights.
Must've really cursed them to death, huh?
Well, even if someone else did the deed,
these guys could always just say
it was the work of their curses.
I see. That's one way to look at it.
Man, speaking of people
who could take on the Dragoons...
The Dragon Slayer and the
leopardman at the colosseum.
What about the Witch of Taboos?
What, the witch?
Yeah! She's a dark elf, right?
Though no one's seen her
in over a decade now.
Actually, someone right here
in the royal capital has met her.
Mind telling me more about that?
Who the hell are you, man?
Oh, first, each of you can
order two drinks of your choice.
Place an order for something to eat, too.
My treat, of course.
All right, young man, have a seat!
Hey, lady! Bring us another round!
So, the person who claims
they've met the Witch of Taboos
is apparently Monroy's
strongest bloodsport warrior.
How would I go about meeting this person?
That monster's gotta be at
the bloodsport colosseum, right?
If you talk to Duke Zuan,
the guy who runs the place—
Boy, you're in luck.
That right there is Monroy's
strongest bloodsport warrior...
EVE SPEED
LEOPARDMAN BLOODSPORT WARRIOR
- Eve Speed.
EVE SPEED
LEOPARDMAN BLOODSPORT WARRIOR
Can I treat you to anything?
I heard the rumors about you
and was hoping to meet you.
My name is Hati. I'm a mercenary.
Eve Speed.
You can really put it away, huh?
Oh, right, you're a bloodsport warrior.
State your business.
You didn't come over here
because I'm a bloodsport warrior.
Or am I wrong?
Saw right through me, huh?
Then I'll be upfront.
Do you know where the Witch of Taboos is?
So you're the type to believe
rumors flying around, huh?
It's true I ventured to the Land of
Golden-Eyed Monsters where she dwells,
but I've never met the witch.
So you're saying that you don't
know where the Witch of Taboos is?
Sorry, but I don't.
I see.
Why do you seek the Witch of Taboos?
Curiosity, I suppose?
I dream of being a scholar in the future.
So I'd love to hire a mercenary
and pay the witch a visit.
That's not a place you waltz into
and come back alive.
I know this sounds rude,
but I doubt you'd last three days there.
I appreciate your concern.
Hmph. I'm just doing you a favor.
From what I can tell, you're still young.
You should cherish your life.
Though maybe that rings hollow
coming from a bloodsport warrior.
She was lying.
So by denying it,
she actually outed herself to us.
Yes. This has to mean...
Eve Speed knows the whereabouts
of the Witch of Taboos.
Oh no.
What's the matter?
I forgot to bring Piggymaru food.
Huh?
It's been a while, but I guess I'll use that.
Slightly hardened bread...
and is this cheese?
It's delicious.
What is this?
Is it a common food in your world?
It is.
P-Pardon me.
Enjoying this otherworldy snack?
Yes. It's so good it made me smile.
I'd love to give you more,
but sadly I can't will it
to produce the same thing.
A transparent bag...
Are these letters scribed on it?
It's pretty.
Maybe it seems more alluring
because it's not from your world.
Now, let's consider our plan moving forward.
Yes.
First up, the Witch of Taboos' location.
I hope we can find a way to get that
bloodsport warrior to tell us, but...
Shall we try gathering information
on her tomorrow?
What would a bloodsport warrior
value most after their life?
Typically money?
They can buy their freedom
if they have the funds.
Though it seems to require a vast sum.
A vast sum, huh?
Anything new?
No.
Hang in there a little longer.
I promise I'll get you out of here.
Silfigzea, Ferillbanger, Willozega.
Every time I see this, it reminds me of
a magical girl's transformation scene.
What gorgeous swordsmanship.
No wonder Civit had high
hopes for fighting her.
So, is there any kind of trick
to close combat?
Are you interested?
I rely too much on my skill as things stand.
I might need it at some point.
I understand.
We'll start with using minimal
motion to lock down your opponent.
What is it?
Well, back when I was captain of the knights,
I often trained the members like this.
So I suddenly felt nostalgic.
Now then...
Please assault me.
Oh, no, um...
I only meant in terms of
using force to defeat me.
I know. Here I come.
Now, if you do this as well...
You don't need any weapons for this,
and you can use it on opponents
you don't want to harm seriously.
You can hone this move
in a few short days...
I-I'm sorry!
I got too close and I'm all sweaty!
Don't worry about it.
If you don't want to get so close,
then please at least teach me the form.
S-Sir Tooka, are you all right
with me teaching you like this?
Yeah, I'm fine with it.
Let's keep going.
Sir Tooka's...
What a strange sensation.
It feels like part of him
is blending into me...
What am I...?
It doesn't look like anyone is watching.
Even if I do have affection for him,
how could I do such a dirty, lewd thing?
Do you have a moment?
Since when—?!
H-How long has Sir Tooka been here?
I'm sorry I didn't notice you were there.
Did you need me for something?
Yeah, I noticed my clothes were missing,
so I wanted to check with you.
My apologies!
I know I didn't ask, but I thought I
would wash them with mine!
You don't mind if I ask you to do that?
I don't mind at all!
I'm used to washing clothes.
That's what a truly kind person looks like.
Seras is diligently trying
to become my sword.
She's suppressing all kinds of emotions
to perform her role for me.
I should be grateful.
Sir Tooka?
Are you still awake?
I just couldn't sleep.
That's not good.
In that case...
These are a type of medicinal herb.
Do they help you go to sleep?
That's correct.
Looks like there are several varieties.
Yes. These herbs have a similar color,
but they have the opposite effect.
Drinking these is said to grant
you vigor and leave you excited.
I'm sorry.
Um, I didn't mean anything by that.
I know.
Medicinal herbs, huh?
Wait a minute.
Oh, that smells good.
Would you like a taste
before we add the herbs?
Yes, please!
It's delicious!
So just putting this
in hot water creates soup?
Seems like an excellent portable meal.
Let's try adding the herbs next.
Yes, right away.
It's done.
Shall I drink the one we
used the wrong amount in?
No, I'll drink it!
Please let me take responsibility.
Okay...
It may be a bit thick after
using the wrong amount,
but drinking this is refreshing.
Refreshing?
Isn't it?
This herb typically...
Did you use the wrong one?
Yes...
Sir Tooka, I'm truly sorry.
It's fine.
Thanks to that, I can read through
a bit more of this tonight.
Damn, I can't seem to settle down.
Um...
Is there anything I can do for you?
Just get some sleep.
We have intel to gather tomorrow.
Sir Tooka.
May I ask you something?
What is it?
Are you resistant to temptation?
Oh, I mean, um...
Well, I might be resistant for now.
For now?
Right now, my revenge takes
priority over all else.
I think that makes it difficult for me
to turn my attention elsewhere.
In a sense, it's binding me.
Binding you?
Though once I achieve my revenge,
I should be able to focus on other things.
Until then...
Well, I guess it's like I'm cursed.
I'll do everything in my power to help
release you from that curse as soon as we can.
Yeah, I'll be counting on you.
Yes, my liege.
BLOODSPORT COLOSSEUM
I've returned.
How did it go?
As you'd expect concerning
a popular bloodsport warrior,
everyone was happy to talk
when I brought up Eve Speed.
She used to be a slave,
and her slaver sold her to the colosseum.
Since leopardmen are uncommon,
she was a hit from her first fight.
Also, she hasn't lost a single
match in the three years since.
Did you already hear that
tomorrow's her final fight?
Yes.
Which means she's already earned
enough to buy her own freedom.
That'll make using money
to negotiate rather difficult.
Moreover, I learned something concerning.
Apparently, she'd already earned the funds
to buy her own freedom two years ago.
Then why...?
She's trying to buy someone else's.
A child?
She wants her freedom too.
There's one more thing you should know.
The majority of previous bloodsport champions
have died during their final matches.
I heard about that too.
But isn't that just the result
of getting pitted against
a challenging opponent for a finale?
It seems there's more to it than that.
I heard the duke running
the bloodsport colosseum
arranges for the champions
to be at a disadvantage.
Then that might be our lead.
TOGETHER WITH THE LORD OF FLIES